Structs, short for structures,
结构体，Structs是structures的缩写，
are custom types that group related data together,
是将相关数据（如冰球运动员的所有属性）
such as all of the attributes of a hockey player. Recall the primitive data types from module 4 –
组合在一起的自定义类型。回想一下第4节中的基本数据类型，
we'll be building structs by putting primitive data types
我们将通过将基本数据类型组合在一起来构建结构体。
We'll be comparing and contrasting
我们将对比
structs with enums,
结构体和在第7讲
which we covered in module 7. In this module, we'll cover when structs are useful;
介绍过的枚举。在本节中，我们将介绍什么时候结构体是适合用的；
we'll
我们将
look at the syntax for defining and using a struct;
学习定义和使用结构体的语法；
we'll also discuss some other forms of structs,
我们还将讨论其他形式的结构体，
which are tuple structs and unit structs.
即tuple结构体和unit结构体（译者注：术语不翻译）。
We'll also briefly circle back to enums to show how you can define enum variants to have named
我们还将简要回顾一下枚举，说明如何定义带字段名称的枚举值，
fields like structs do.
就像结构体一样。
Let's get started with when structs are useful.
让我们从结构体何时适合用开始，
Remember the HockeyPosition
还记得我们
enum
undefined 在上一讲创建的 HockeyPosition 枚举吗？
Let's say we now want to create a data type that models a
假设我们想要创建一个数据类型来为
hockey player –
冰球运动员建模，
that would be a good fit for a struct.
这个场景将非常适合用结构体来描述。
Every hockey player has a bunch of attributes that describe that player.
每个冰球运动员都有一堆属性来描述他。
They each have a name,
每个人都有一个名字，
a number,
一个号码，
a position, and some stats like how many goals they've scored this year.
一个球场位置，以及一些其他数据，比如他们今年进了多少球。
This set of attributes is the same across all players,
所有运动员都有这些同样的属性，
but each player has different values for these attributes.
但每个球员的属性值都不同。
Putting values for these attributes together describes a particular hockey player.
将这些属性值放在一起，就能描述出一名特定的冰球运动员。
Describing a hockey player with a struct is a better fit than describing a hockey player with an enum
用结构体来表示一个冰球运动员比用枚举要更适合，
because we're not choosing between different kinds of hockey players.
因为我们不是在不同种类的冰球运动员中进行选择。
An enum is for when you want to describe a choice between a set of values,
当在一组值中做选择时，
such as choosing banana,
例如香蕉、
apple, or orange from a set of fruits.
苹果和橙子，可以使用枚举。
A struct is for when you want to have the same attributes for all of the values of that type,
当希望该类型所有值都具有相同的属性时，
such as multiple recipes that all have a list of ingredients and a list of directions.
例如多个食谱都有成分列表和说明列表时，可以使用结构体。
Let's look at how we define a hockey player struct in code.
让我们看看如何在代码中定义冰球运动员结构体。
A struct definition starts with the struct keyword,
结构体定义以 struct 关键字开头，
then the name we want to use for the struct.
然后是我们想要用于该结构体的名称。
Here, we've picked HockeyPlayer. Struct names, by convention, should be camel case.
在这里，我们选择 HockyPlayer 作为结构体名称。按照惯例，结构体名称应该采用驼峰命名风格。
Next comes curly brackets, and, within them,
接下来是大括号，大括号内是以逗号分隔的
a comma-separated list of the field names and types that make up the struct.
字段名和字段类型的列表。
Field names should be in snake case.
字段名称应采用蛇形命名法。
For HockeyPlayer, we've got a name field that's a String, a number field that's a u8, a position field that has the type of our HockeyPosition enum,
对于 HockeyPlayer，我们有一个字符串类型的名称字段，一个 u8 类型的数字字段，一个 HocyerPosition 枚举类型的位置字段，
and a goals year-to-date field that is also u8.
以及一个也是 u8 类型的今年进球数的字段。
Now it's time to put this struct definition to use.
现在是时候使用这个结构体定义了。
Struct definitions list the set of attributes,
结构体定义列出了属性集，
and we can then fill in a struct with values to represent a particular instance. To instantiate
接着我们可以用值填充结构体来表示特定实例。为了实例化
a particular hockey player and store the data in a variable,
一个特定的冰球运动员并将数据存储在变量中，
we set the variable equal to the struct name,
我们写变量名，等于号和结构体名称，
then open curly brackets,
然后是大括号，
then list each field and the value we want each field to have.
然后列出每个字段以及希望设置的值。
Remember to finish the assignment statement with a semicolon.
记住，以分号结束赋值语句。
It's required to initialize all the fields of the struct with the value.
需要用值初始化结构体的所有字段。
Once we have a struct instance,
一旦我们有了一个结构体实例，
we can access the value in a particular field of the struct by using the variable name, then a dot, then the field we want to access.
我们就可以通过使用变量名，然后是一个点，然后是我们想要访问的字段来访问该结构体的特定字段中的值。
We can also change the values
只要实例是可变的，
in an instance's
我们就可以
fields as long as the instance is mutable.
更改实例字段中的值。
This code adds one to the goals year-to-date field,
这段代码为今年进球数字段加一，
and the program now printsBryan Rust has scored 8 goals this season.
现在程序打印“Bryan Rust has scored 8 goals this season”。
Having named fields is what most structs look like,
大多数结构体都有命名字段，
but there are also tuple structs and unit structs.
但也有元组结构体和单元结构体。
Let's look at those briefly. Tuple
让我们简单了解了一下这些结构。
structs are structs that have a name for the whole type but don't name their fields.
元组结构体是指光有类型但没字段名称的结构体。
They behave similarly to tuples.
元组结构体的行为与元组类似。
You access their fields with a dot and an index,
你可以使用点和索引来访问他们的字段，
starting with zero.
索引从零开始。
For example,
例如，
here's a tuple struct named Triangle,
这里有个名为 Triangle 的元组，
defined to store the length of each of the three sides of a triangle.
定义为存储三角形三边的长度。
Tuple
就 Rust 的类型检查器而言，元组结构体可用于创建被认为与普通元组
as far as Rust's type checker is concerned.
或其他元组结构不同的类型。
We can't pass a plain tuple to this function that only takes a Triangle.
我们不能将一个普通的元组传递给这个只需要一个 Triangle 元组结构体类型参数的函数。
If we try,
如果这样做了，
we get a type error.
会收到类型错误。
Giving the tuple a name by using a tuple struct has made this a new type incompatible with other tuples.
通过使用元组结构体来给元组命名，使其成为与其他元组不兼容的新类型。
One common use of a tuple struct is called the newtype pattern,
元组结构体的一种常见用法称为 newtype 模式，
where an existing type is wrapped in a tuple struct with one element to add meaning.
即用元组结构体包装现有类型，并添加一个元素以增加含义。
An example of this is wrapping
例如，我们将
a u8 in a struct named Meters,
u8 封装在名为 Meters 的结构体中，
which now guarantees that, in places that use values of type Meters,
这就保证了在使用 Meters 类型值的地方，
we can't use a plain
我们不能使用普通的 u8 变量。
If we try to compile this code that attempts to call a function that takes Meters with a plain u8,
如果我们尝试编译这段试图调用一个使用普通 u8 的 Meters 函数的代码，
we'll get a type error.
会得到类型错误。
This can prevent bugs caused by accidentally using values that are in the wrong units.
这可以防止因意外使用某个错误的值而导致的 bug。
Structs actually don't need to have any fields. Structs without
结构体实际上不需要任何字段。没有字段的
fields are called unit
结构体称为单元结构体。
Unit
单元结构体似乎现在还看不出有什么用，
but you can define methods on them.
但你可以为它们定义方法。
We're going to talk about methods in the next module.
我们将在下一节谈论方法。
One last thing:
最后一件事：
now that we've seen what structs with named fields look like,
既然我们已经看到带有命名字段的结构体的样子，
let's look at
那么让我们来看看
enum variants that can have named fields like structs.
像结构体一样带有命名字段的枚举。
Remember the clock example from the last module?
还记得上一节中的时种示例吗？
Each variant held values representing hours,
每个变体都有代表小时、
minutes, or seconds.
分钟或秒的值。
But it was hard to tell which field meant which value – you just had to know.
但是很难分辨哪个字段代表哪个值 - 而这就是需要知道的。
We can make this better by making these variants more like a struct and adding field names.
我们可以让这些变体更像结构体，并添加字段名称，这样就能让效果更好。
We also have to change the parentheses to curly brackets.
我们还必须将括号改为大括号。
In this module, we covered
这本节中，
when to use structs versus enums,
我们介绍了何时使用结构体与枚举，
how to declare and use structs, tuple and unit
如何声明和使用结构体、元组和
structs, and enum variants
单元结构体，以及
that look like structs.
看起来像结构体的枚举变体。
That's how structs work in Rust.
这就是结构体在 Rust 中的使用方式。
Go forth and organize your data into new types.
去吧，把你的数据组织成新的类型
Next,
下一节，
we'll talk about adding behavior to structs and enums by defining methods on them.
我们将讨论如何通过在结构体和枚举上定义方法来为它们添加行为。